Guide to the Photographs by and relating to Allen Ginsberg MSS.PHOTO.0450
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 2: Contact Sheets, Series 2
  - Contact sheet 1313, 1990 Apr. 22; 1313 (Item 25)
    "Cambridge, MA; Silverglate Family, Isaac's bar mitzvah party; in side yard Silverglate's garden/driveway Franklin at Cambridge"
    Andrea Dworkin
  - Contact sheet 1314, 1990 Apr. 26; 1314 (Item 25)
    New York City; 1-4 painter and Natan Zach in my house; 5-8 old St. Marks baths (closed) J.F. Cooper's residence; 9-10 Susie Rashkes; 11 Jack Shuai Shu; 18-22 what poet?; 23-30 Fracus (fight) on Brooklyn College quadrangle; street scenes
  - Contact sheet 1315, 1990 Apr. 28; 1315 (Item 25)
    "East Berlin, Germany; Prague, Czechoslovakia; 11-28 East Berlin (for photo show?); Sacha Anderson and friends; 23-31 Anne Waldman reading in East Berlin at my photo show (Kammerspeile?), Istvan Eorsi and company; 32-37 Prague, Nanao Sakaki and Japanese music group, bus ride thru Temelin Nuclear plant to Budovic for reading with ex Plastic-People band"
  - Contact sheet 1316, 1990 Apr. 28; 1316 (Item 25)
    "Czechoslovakia; Pulnosz band, bus to temelin, on way to Budovice concert in Czechoslovakia; street scenes"
  - Contact sheet 1317, 1990 Apr. 29; 1317 (Item 25)
    "Czechoslovakia; Cesto Budovice concert with Pulnosz; Prague Stare mesto?, Olomouc Square? Cesto Budovice"
  - Contact sheet 1318, 1990 May 1; 1318 (Item 25)
    "Prague, Czechoslovakia; May Day 1990; 1-19 table with Havel at foot of Main St.; 20-36 Stace Maesto Sq., return of May King Ceremony"
  - Contact sheet 1319, 1990 May 3; 1319 (Item 25)
    "Prague, Czechoslovakia; 1-4 Andy Clausen; 5-11 Charles Bridge with Nanao Sakaki's music group on subway, Anne Waldman; friend, Andy Clausen; 19-36 Charles University reading"
    Charles University
  - Contact sheet 1320, 1990 May 3; 1320 (Item 25)
    "Prague, Czechoslovakia; 1-8 reading in nightclub Prague w/ Philnosc-Ulasova Concert Hall, Nanao Sakaki and friends where they stayed; 11-16 Maria and Eva Zabranova (Jan Zabrana's widow, daughter) (my Czech translator 1965- ); 18 Jiri Josek, Istvan Eorsi, Nanao Sakaki, Dr. Joe Gross; 19-36 Vaclav Havel and Anne Waldman conversation May Day, Nanao background with Jap-Czech friend; Havel examining translation of Kral Majales; Olomouc"
    Philnosc-Ulasova Concert Hall
  - Contact sheet 1321, 1990 May 4; 1321 (Item 25)
    "Prague, Czechoslovakia; Olomouc Paluscheho University; Anne Waldman 15-18 with friend; Josef Jarab, rector 10-11, 23; 26-32 drive to Prague; 33-36 poetry reading bookstore Prague; 26-32 our interpreter who told me "Poe" story and had led student revolt in Olomouc"
    Olomouc Paluscheho University
  - Contact sheet 1322, 1990 May 4; 1322 (Item 25)
    "Prague, Czechoslovakia; Anne Waldman poetry reading bookstore 1-31, 35-36 E. German poets? E. Berlin?"
  - Contact sheet 1323, 1990 May 30; 1323 (Item 25)
    "Prague, Czechoslovakia; South bohemia on way to Cesto Budovice?, Anne Waldman, friend visit to castle; 12 Nanao Sakaki in tree back house; 21 whole company; street scenes"
  - Contact sheet 1324, 1990 May 7; 1324 (Item 25)
    "New York City; friends of Gelek, NY hosts; kitchen window scenes"
  - Contact sheet 1325.1, 1990 May 12; 1325.1 (Item 25)
    "Mt. Tremper, NY; Zen Mountain Center"
  - Contact sheet 1325.2, 1990 May 13; 1325.2 (Item 25)
    John Daido Laorie
  - Contact sheet 1326, 1990 May 16; 1326 (Item 25)
    New York City; rainy kitchen window views; American Academy Cermonial May 1990; Hale Ceremony
  - Contact sheet 1327, 1990 May 16; 1327 (Item 25)
    "New York City; Mt. Tremper, NY; 10th St. Japanese restaurant; Mt. Tremper; Anne Waldman in her room; Dohusan Room; 31 Lewis Hyde; kitchen window views"
  - Contact sheet 1328, 1990 May 16; 1328 (Item 25)
    "New York City; Mt. Tremper, NY; Academy Convocation (May 16); Mary Help of Christians Church window (May 19); 2nd Ave."
  - Contact sheet 1329, 1990 May 23; 1329 (Item 25)
    New York City; street scenes; skyscrapers; 437 E. 12th St. apartment building
  - Contact sheet 1330, 1990 May 25; 1330 (Item 25)
    "Charleston, SC; Spoleto Festival; 1-13 Cambridge Cigarette Flag sign; Philip Glass and Hydrogen Jukebox stage; 25-32 Eugene and Connie Brooks with local friends, Mr. and Mrs. Ted Phillips (141 Church St., Charleston, SC 29401); cemetery graveyard"
  - Contact sheet 1331, 1990 May 30; 1331 (Item 25)
    "Charleston, SC; Spoleto Festival visit; sightseeing; horse cart tour; cemetery"
  - Contact sheet 1332, 1990 June 4; 1332 (Item 25)
    New York City; Our birthday supper Eugene Brooks house; kitchen window views; homeless street panhandler/reader; Mary Help of Christians Church window; Robert Frank in my front room
  - Contact sheet 1333, 1990 June 3; 1333 (Item 25)
    "New York City; Charleston, SC; Paterson, NJ; Spoleto festival; 8-10 outdoor cafe Allen Ginsberg, Philip Glass, Gelek Rinpoche, Cathy Laritz; 18-21 strange kid traveler I met, at my house Charleston; street scenes E. 12th St. between 1st and A, 437 E. 12th building; Jack Shuai Shu at Metropolitan Museum; 34-36 Edith Ginsberg at kitchen table, Elmwood Terrace"
  - Contact sheet 1334, 1990 June 3; 1334 (Item 25)
    "New York City; Tienanmen Square rally, Chinese consulate 10th Ave."
  - Contact sheet 1335, 1990 June 4; 1335 (Item 25)
    New York City; V. Kress household kitchen
  - Contact sheet 1336, 1990 June 15; 1336 (Item 25)
    "New York City; London, England; 2nd Ave. and 9th St.; London from Tower Records 2nd floor; Miles and Steven Taylor, he had to take photos of publishers for his job in NY"
  - Contact sheet 1337, 1990 June 17; 1337 (Item 25)
    "London, England; Soho street scenes"
  - Contact sheet 1338, 1990 June 19; 1338 (Item 25)
    "Istanbul, Turkey; Strait of Bosporus"
  - Contact sheet 1339, 1990 June 19; 1339 (Item 25)
    "Istanbul, Turkey; Munich, Germany; Strait of Bosporus; Hagra Sophia Church"
  - Contact sheet 1340, 1990 June 20; 1340 (Item 25)
    "Istanbul, Turkey; Munich, Germany; Yasar Kemal; 3-13 restaurant alley Istanbul with poets; 19-20 rug buying with Kurt Muncasci; 17-18 poet and newspaper roof"
  - Contact sheet 1341, 1990 June 21; 1341 (Item 25)
    "Istanbul, Turkey; Ephesus; street scenes"
  - Contact sheet 1342, 1990 June 22; 1342 (Item 25)
    "Selcuk, Turkey; "
  - Contact sheet 1343, 1990 June 23; 1343 (Item 25)
    "Aphrodesia, Turkey"
  - Contact sheet 1344.1, 1990 June 23; 1344.1 (Item 25)
    "Ephesus, Turkey; Muslum, Pergamon"
  - Contact sheet 1344.2, 6/25/1990; 1344.2 (Item 25)
    "COLOR: Ankara, Turkey; Spoleto, Italy"
  - Contact sheet 1345, 1990 June 26; 1345 (Item 25)
    "Ankara, Turkey; Coppodocia"
  - Contact sheet 1346, 1990 June 27; 1346 (Item 25)
    "Ankara, Turkey; Cappodocia"
  - Contact sheet 1347, 1990 June 30; 1347 (Item 25)
    "Spoleto, Italy; Benn Posset of One World Poetry and his son; Spoleto Church, Theater Square"
  - Contact sheet 1348, 1990 July 5; 1348 (Item 25)
    "Rome, Italy; New York City; Boulder, CO; Nanda Pivano and her house and friend; 6-11; Vatican City; 12-18 Piazza Navona; 22 Campo di Fiore; 25-36 Naropa; 30-36 Gary Snyder lecturing; Bellevue Hospital buildings; religious store windows"
  - Contact sheet 1349, 1990 July 6; 1349 (Item 25)
    "Boulder, CO; Party Naropa"
  - Contact sheet 1350, 1990 July 16; 1350 (Item 25)
    "Boulder, CO; Picnic with Jack Shuai Shu at Anne's?; parking lot; Harry Smith lecturing; Peter Lamborn Wilson and Steven Taylor attending; picnic (Anselm Hollo's garden yard?)"
  - Contact sheet 1351, 1990 July 6; 1351 (Item 26)
    "New York City; windows broken by Peter Orlovsky at 437 E. 12th St., his kitchen as he kept it Apt. 24 (July 6-7)"
  - Contact sheet 1352, 1990 July 7; 1352 (Item 26)
    "Boulder, CO; Saturday Symposium"
  - Contact sheet 1353, 1990 July 7; 1353 (Item 26)
  - Contact sheet 1354, 1990 July 7; 1354 (Item 26)
  - Contact sheet 1355, 1990 July 8; 1355 (Item 26)
  - Contact sheet 1356, 1990 July 9; 1356 (Item 26)
  - Contact sheet 1357, 1990 July 9; 1357 (Item 26)
    "Boulder, CO; tent at Naropa"
  - Contact sheet 1358, 1990 July 9; 1358 (Item 26)
  - Contact sheet 1359, 1990 July 9; 1359 (Item 26)
  - Contact sheet 1360, 1990 July 9; 1360 (Item 26)
  - Contact sheet 1361, 1990 July 9; 1361 (Item 26)
    "Boulder, CO; symposium in tent"
  - Contact sheet 1362, 1990 July 10; 1362 (Item 26)
  - Contact sheet 1363, 1990 July 14; 1363 (Item 26)
    "Boulder, CO; Lawrence Ferlinghetti reading"
  - Contact sheet 1364, 1990 July 19; 1364 (Item 26)
    "Boulder, CO; Anne Waldman and students"
  - Contact sheet 1365, 1990 July 19; 1365 (Item 26)
    "Boulder, CO; Santa Fe, NM; Lunch with Anne Waldman and Bobbie Louise Hawkins?; Mei Mei Bersenbregese and husband etching factory"
  - Contact sheet 1366, 1990 July 20; 1366 (Item 26)
    "Boulder, CO; Santa Fe, NM; Anselm Hollo's party or Anne's house; Etching Workshop Santa Fe?"
  - Contact sheet 1367, 1990 July 20; 1367 (Item 26)
    "Santa Fe, NM; Burroughs/Ginsberg Photo Art Show, Steven Lowe's Gallery"
  - Contact sheet 1368, 1990 July 21; 1368 (Item 26)
    "Santa Fe, NM; Burroughs/Ginsberg Photo Art Show, Steven Lowe's Gallery; party at Maggie Kress' house; Ginsberg reading to guests (Jack Shuai Shu with my camera?)"
  - Contact sheet 1369, 1990 July 22; 1369 (Item 26)
    "Santa Fe, NM"
  - Contact sheet 1370, 1990 July 23; 1370 (Item 26)
    "Boulder, CO; Santa Fe, NM; Naropa picnic"
  - Contact sheet 1371, 1990 July 23; 1371 (Item 26)
    "Boulder, CO; Santa Fe, NM; Larry Littlebird in gallery; Naropa folksinger/Buddhist Peter Rowan; picnic"
  - Contact sheet 1372, 1990 July 29; 1372 (Item 26)
    "Boulder, CO; Naropa Colloquium"
  - Contact sheet 1373, 1990 July 30; 1373 (Item 26)
    "Boulder, CO; Naropa Symposium; Rocky Mountain Dharma Center #8-24 with stupa (circumambulation); 8 with Beverley Isis and 29-30; 22 Anne Waldman and Reed Bye; 31-33 mask shop (with Anne's son); 36 Tom Peters, Beat Bookshop window group"
  - Contact sheet 1374, 1990 Aug. 4; 1374 (Item 26)
    "Boulder, CO; New York City; office in New York; kitchen window views; Allen Ginsberg self portrait; Union Square office window views; skyline"
  - Contact sheet 1375, 1990 Aug. 4; 1375 (Item 26)
    "Boulder, CO; New York City; Tom Peters Bookshop; street person; Jefferson Theater 14th St.; 8 PM kitchen window views"
  - Contact sheet 1376, 1990 Aug. 8; 1376 (Item 26)
    New York City; kitchen window views; windows broken by Peter Orlovsky; Allen Ginsberg self portraits in bed
  - Contact sheet 1378, 1990 Aug. 7; 1378 (Item 26)
    "Boulder, CO; New York City; window Peter Orlovsky broke; front door of 437 E. 12th St.; Allen Ginsberg self portrait"
  - Contact sheet 1379, 1990 Aug. 7; 1379 (Item 26)
    New York City; apartment destroyed by Peter Orlovsky; Mary Help of Christians Church window funeral
  - Contact sheet 1380, 1990 Aug. 12; 1380 (Item 26)
    New York City; apartment destroyed by Peter Orlovsky; store windows; Key Pharmacy pharmacist on 14th & Ave. A; 1-3 night window; 4-12 Peter's apt.; 24-26 Herbert Huncke; 27 Edith Ginsberg in her kitchen; 28-29 homeless street lady; 30-36 kitchen window views
  - Contact sheet 1381, 1990 Aug. 23; 1381 (Item 26)
    "New York City; Seoul, South Korea; 1-12 Peter Orlovsky, Bellevue or VA Hospital, showing burns on leg from arrest on hot steam manhole; 13 "Fart Spray" Joke store window E 18/19th St.; 16 Jacqueline Gens, Beverley Isis, Gelek Rinpoche E 12th St. going to eat at KK's to 22 at KK's restaurant 1st Ave.; 29-36 Seoul South Korea, Bei Dao and Andrei Vosnesensky press conference"
  - Contact sheet 1382, 1990 Aug. 24; 1382 (Item 26)
    "Seoul, South Korea; Elephant in Courtyard; shrine"
  - Contact sheet 1383, 1990 Aug. 24; 1383 (Item 26)
    "Seoul, South Korea"
  - Contact sheet 1384, 1990 Aug. 25; 1384 (Item 26)
    "Seoul, South Korea; museum statues; garden scenes"
  - Contact sheet 1385, 1990 Aug. 26; 1385 (Item 26)
    "Seoul, South Korea; meeting with Kim Chi Ha, ex-jail radical poet and translators"
  - Contact sheet 1386, 1990 Aug. 28; 1386 (Item 26)
    "Seoul, South Korea; street scenes"
  - Contact sheet 1387, 1990 Aug. 29; 1387 (Item 26)
    Bei Dao
  - Contact sheet 1388, 1990 Sept. 1; 1388 (Item 26)
    "Seoul, South Korea; East Sea Korea; Shin Hungsa temple; mountains and village views"
  - Contact sheet 1389, 1990 Sept. 1; 1389 (Item 26)
    Waterloo Village? New Jersey; NJ Festival (Dodge); ten Quincy Troupe?; Professor Music at Brooklyn College
    Bei Dao; Brooklyn College
  - Contact sheet 1390, 1990 Sept. 13; 1390 (Item 26)
    "Paris, France; Miami, FL; Frederic Mitterand TV show; Oleta river; Miami Book Fair"
  - Contact sheet 1391, 1990 Sept. 13; 1391 (Item 26)
    "Paris, France; Miami, FL; Frederic Mitterand TV show"
  - Contact sheet 1392, 1990 Sept. 20; 1392 (Item 26)
    "Washington, DC; NJ; New York City; owner of Village Voice (#15)"
  - Contact sheet 1393, 1990 Sept. 15; 1393 (Item 26)
    "Waterloo Village?, NJ; Seoul, South Korea; Bei Dao at Dodge Festival with Chinese poets and translators; kitchen window views"
    Bei Dao; Jacqueline Gens
  - Contact sheet 1394, 1990 Sept. 20; 1394 (Item 26)
    "Waterloo Village?, Washington, NJ; group photos with Dalai Lama"
  - Contact sheet 1395, 1990 Oct. 10; 1395 (Item 26)
    New York City; Francesco Clemente's studio
  - Contact sheet 1396, 1990 Oct. 10; 1396 (Item 26)
    New York City; Julian Schnabel and parents
  - Contact sheet 1397, 1990 Oct. 13; 1397 (Item 26)
    "Seattle, WA; Portland, OR; Portland Born Again Convention Meeting"
  - Contact sheet 1398, 1990 Oct. 17; 1398 (Item 26)
    "New York City; Paterson, NJ; National Arts Club"
    National Arts Club
  - Contact sheet 1399, 1990 Oct. 20; 1399 (Item 26)
    "New York City; Bob Dylan concert, Beacon Theater; Reading at Shakespeare and Co. Bookshop with Eileen Myles (Oct. 19); subway views"
  - Contact sheet 1400, 1990 Oct. 20; 1400 (Item 26)
  - Contact sheet 1401, 1990 Oct. 25; 1401 (Item 27)
    "Philadelphia, PA; Allen Ginsberg self portrait"
  - Contact sheet 1402, 1990 Oct. 26; 1402 (Item 27)
    Quincy Troupe; Costey McAurtry
  - Contact sheet 1403, 1990 Oct. 28; 1403 (Item 27)
  - Contact sheet 1404, 1990 Oct. 28; 1404 (Item 27)
    "New York City; Philadelphia, PA; Philadelphia Museum of Art entrance; Chenchen Achebe Benefit; kitchen window views"
  - Contact sheet 1405, 1990 Nov. 3; 1405 (Item 27)
    New York City?; street scenes; Allen Ginsberg self portrait
  - Contact sheet 1406, 1990 Nov. 4; 1406 (Item 27)
    New York City; Union Square office window; skyline
    June Leaf; Robert Frank
  - Contact sheet 1407, 1990 Nov. 6; 1407 (Item 27)
    "Paris, France; New York City; Brooklyn College; graffiti; Shakespeare and Co Bookshop (2nd floor fire); kids in Paris; Deux Megots"
  - Contact sheet 1408, 1990 Nov. 7; 1408 (Item 27)
    "Paris, France; street scenes; Allen Ginsberg reading"
  - Contact sheet 1409, 1990 Nov. 9; 1409 (Item 27)
    "Paris, France; Island Folk, Mercaurant le Charpentier; 11-13 Paris Paule Thevenin, after supper; interviewer from Gay Pieds at Brasserie Lipp and Allen Ginsberg; 17-19 Alain Jouffroi, Hotel des Navronieres; 20-21 Michel Bulteau; 22 supper at Christine's; 23-30 restaurant/Brasserie corner Rue Bonaparte and Rue Jacob, J.J. Lebel and Yves Le Pellec; restaurant - Christine Ritchory? and husband; self portraits"
    Hotel des Navronieres
  - Contact sheet 1410, 1990 Nov. 11; 1410 (Item 27)
    "Paris, France; Island Records supper; Allen Ginsberg self portrait"
  - Contact sheet 1411, 1990 Nov. 12; 1411 (Item 27)
    "Paris, France; Larry Litzky's house, Paris (suburb); hotel in Paris; Mrs. Jean Claude Mayer at home; Rue Git Le Coeur; Oceanique Film Crew"
  - Contact sheet 1412, 1990 Nov. 12; 1412 (Item 27)
    "Paris, France; lady friend from lunch with Jean-Claude Mayer; Paul Bowles and boy from Paris; Rue Git Le Coeur"
  - Contact sheet 1413, 1990 Nov. 13; 1413 (Item 27)
    "Paris, France; Nam June Paik's friends, printmakers Paris basement Marroniers Hotel; Breton's house?"
    Hotel des Marroniers
  - Contact sheet 1414, 1990 Nov. 15; 1414 (Item 27)
    "Paris, France; Gualtari's supper party; Allen Ginsberg self portrait"
  - Contact sheet 1415, 1990 Nov. 18; 1415 (Item 27)
    "Miami, FL; Miami Book Fair"
  - Contact sheet 1416, 1990 Nov. 20; 1416 (Item 27)
    New York City; Deux Megot St. Germain des Pres; homeless; street scenes; kitchen window views
  - Contact sheet 1417, 1990 Nov. 26; 1417 (Item 27)
    New York City; Ghandi Restaurant 6th St. and 1st Ave.; kitchen window views; George Schneeman's party
  - Contact sheet 1418, 1990 Nov. 27; 1418 (Item 27)
  - Contact sheet 1419, 1990 Nov. 28; 1419 (Item 27)
    New York City; street person
    Nam June Paik; Jack Shuai Shu
  - Contact sheet 1420, 1990 Dec. 2; 1420 (Item 27)
    New York City; Albany Cherry Valley; Gregory Corso and Raymond Foye at Small Press Book Fair; Small Press Bookfair; Taxi photographer; street person
  - Contact sheet 1421, 1990 Dec. 2; 1421 (Item 27)
    New York City; Gregory Corso and Raymond Foye at Small Press Book Fair
  - Contact sheet 1422, 1990 Dec. 5; 1422 (Item 27)
    New York City; Symphony Space
  - Contact sheet 1423, 1990 Dec. 5; 1423 (Item 27)
  - Contact sheet 1424, 1990 Dec. 6; 1424 (Item 27)
    New York City; Allen Ginsberg by Robert Frank; Reading: Robert Creeley; John Ashbery; introduced by Ron Padgett
  - Contact sheet 1425, 1990 Dec. 6; 1425 (Item 27)
  - Contact sheet 1426, 1990 Dec. 11; 1426 (Item 27)
  - Contact sheet 1427, 1990 Dec. 15; 1427 (Item 27)
  - Contact sheet 1428, 1990 Dec. 16; 1428 (Item 27)
  - Contact sheet 1429, 1990 Dec. 21; 1429 (Item 27)
  - Contact sheet 1430, 1990 Dec. 21; 1430 (Item 27)
  - Contact sheet 1431, 1990 Dec. 22; 1431 (Item 27)
  - Contact sheet 1432, 1990 Dec. 22; 1432 (Item 27)
  - Contact sheet 1433, 1990 Dec. 23; 1433 (Item 27)
  - Contact sheet 1435, 1990 Dec. 29; 1435 (Item 27)
  - Contact sheet 1436, 1990 Dec. 29; 1436 (Item 27)
    New York City; Binghamton State Hospital 7-19; (Dec. 25); Eugene Brooks and family Christmas party
  - Contact sheet 1437, 1990 Dec. 30; 1437 (Item 27)
    "Bath, NY; Allen Ginsberg self portrait; Vatidral Hotel"
  - Contact sheet 1438, 1990 Dec. 31; 1438 (Item 27)
    "Bath, NY"
  - Contact sheet 1439, 1991 Jan. 1; 1439 (Item 27)
  - Contact sheet 1440, 1991 Jan. 1; 1440 (Item 27)
    New York City; St. Marks Poetry Marathon; kitchen window views
  - Contact sheet 1441, 1991 Jan. 1; 1441 (Item 28)
  - Contact sheet 1442, 1991 Jan. 1; 1442 (Item 28)
    "Bath, NY; 2AM Francesco Clemente's party"
  - Contact sheet 1443, 1991 Jan. 1; 1443 (Item 28)
    New York City; Christmas to 1/1/91; kitchen window views
  - Contact sheet 1444, 1991 Jan. 1; 1444 (Item 28)
    New York City; St. Mark's Marathon reading; Cliff Fyman juggling fire
  - Contact sheet 1445, 1991 Jan. 1; 1445 (Item 28)
    New York City; St. Mark's Marathon reading; Cliff Fyman juggling fire; kitchen window views
  - Contact sheet 1446, 1991 Jan. 5; 1446 (Item 28)
  - Contact sheet 1447, 1991 Jan. 5; 1447 (Item 28)
  - Contact sheet 1448, 1991 Jan. 6; 1448 (Item 28)
  - Contact sheet 1449, 1991 Jan. 6; 1449 (Item 28)
  - Contact sheet 1450, 1991 Jan. 6; 1450 (Item 28)
  - Contact sheet 1451, 1991 Jan. 7; 1451 (Item 28)
  - Contact sheet 1452.1, 1991 Jan. 9; 1452.1 (Item 28)
  - Contact sheet 1452.2, 1991 Jan. 10; 1452.2 (Item 28)
  - Contact sheet 1453, 1991 Jan. 11; 1453 (Item 28)
  - Contact sheet 1454, 1991 Jan. 15; 1454 (Item 28)
    New York City; March from Metropolitan Museum to UN; (1/30) XA broken; Mary Help of Christians Church windows; street scenes
  - Contact sheet 1455, 1991 Jan. 15; 1455 (Item 28)
    New York City; (1/15-2/3); Allen Ginsberg self portrait
  - Contact sheet 1456, 1991 Jan. 20; 1456 (Item 28)
    New York City; Allen Ginsberg self portrait; television; Herbert Huncke in Union Square office; photography installation views
  - Contact sheet 1457, 1991 Jan. 21; 1457 (Item 28)
  - Contact sheet 1458, 1991 Jan. 22; 1458 (Item 28)
  - Contact sheet 1459, 1991 Jan. 26; 1459 (Item 28)
    "New York City; Hartford, CT; Wadsworth Atheneum; Allen Ginsberg self portrait; bus views; skyscrapers from Union Square office; Tom Pickard and Allen Ginsberg self portrait"
    Wadsworth Atheneum
  - Contact sheet 1460, 1991 Feb. 1; 1460 (Item 28)
    "New York City; Hartford, CT"
  - Contact sheet 1461, 1991 Feb. 10; 1461 (Item 28)
    New York City; New Jersey
  - Contact sheet 1462, 1991 Feb. 17; 1462 (Item 28)
    David Greenberg
  - Contact sheet 1463, 1991 Feb. 23; 1463 (Item 28)
    "Lexington, VA; Virginia Military Institute; cadets"
    Virginia Military Institute; Daisy Ball; Gordon Ball
  - Contact sheet 1464, 1991 Feb. 28; 1464 (Item 28)
    "New York City; Lexington, VA"
  - Contact sheet 1465, 1991 Mar. 2; 1465 (Item 28)
  - Contact sheet 1466, 1991 Mar. 2; 1466 (Item 28)
  - Contact sheet 1467, 1991 Mar. 4; 1467 (Item 28)
    COLOR: New York City; trip to Leadbelly's grave; subway scenes; 437 E. 12th St. apartment views
  - Contact sheet 1468, 1991 Mar. 4; 1468 (Item 28)
    Arthur Russel
  - Contact sheet 1469, 1991 Mar. 9; 1469 (Item 28)
  - Contact sheet 1470, 1991 Mar. 9; 1470 (Item 28)
    "New York City; Ann Arbor, MI; John Giorno at Brooklyn College; Allen Ginsberg self portrait"
  - Contact sheet 1471, 1991 Mar. 9; 1471 (Item 28)
    "Ann Arbor, MI; cemetery views; Leadbelly tombstones"
  - Contact sheet 1472, 1991 Mar. 11; 1472 (Item 28)
  - Contact sheet 1473, 1991 Mar. 11; 1473 (Item 28)
  - Contact sheet 1474, 1991 Mar. 12; 1474 (Item 28)
    New York City; Gary Snyder at Whitney Museum; at Books and Company reading and book signing; in restaurant with Burton Watson
    Whitney Museum; Books and Company
  - Contact sheet 1475, 1991 Mar. 12; 1475 (Item 28)
    New York City; Brooklyn College Rainbow Reading
  - Contact sheet 1476, 1991 Mar. 12; 1476 (Item 28)
  - Contact sheet 1477, 1991 Mar. 13; 1477 (Item 28)
    New York City; street scenes; Gregory Corso at St. Mark's Church and Brooklyn College
  - Contact sheet 1478, 1991 Mar. 21; 1478 (Item 28)
    Karel Appel
  - Contact sheet 1479, 1991 Mar. 21; 1479 (Item 28)
  - Contact sheet 1480, 1991 Mar. 23; 1480 (Item 28)
    Brooks, Alan
  - Contact sheet 1481, 1991 Mar. 23; 1481 (Item 28)
    "New York City; Elmwood Park, NJ; kitchen window views"
  - Contact sheet 1482, 1991 Mar. 23; 1482 (Item 28)
    "New York City; Elmwood Park, NJ; kitchen window views; Intrepid Aircraft Carrier Museum"
    Intrepid Aircraft Carrier Museum; Edith Brooks
  - Contact sheet 1483, 1991 Mar. 28; 1483 (Item 28)
    "San Francisco, CA; Lawrence Ferlinghetti at City Lights; Larry Eigner at Cody's Books in Berkeley"
    City Lights; Cody's Books
  - Contact sheet 1484, 1991 Mar. 28; 1484 (Item 28)
    New York City; Mary Help of Christians Church window; David Greenberg in theater
  - Contact sheet 1485, 1991 Mar. 28; 1485 (Item 28)
    "New York City; San Francisco, CA; airplane views of San Francisco; Lawrence Ferlinghetti at City Lights"
  - Contact sheet 1486, 1991 Mar. 28; 1486 (Item 28)
  - Contact sheet 1487, 1991 Mar. 28; 1487 (Item 28)
  - Contact sheet 1488, 1991 Mar. 29; 1488 (Item 28)
  - Contact sheet 1489, 1991 Mar. 30; 1489 (Item 28)
  - Contact sheet 1490, 1991 Mar. 31; 1490 (Item 28)
  - Contact sheet 1491, 1991 Mar. 31; 1491 (Item 28)
  - Contact sheet 1492, 1991 Apr. 1; 1492 (Item 28)
  - Contact sheet 1493, 1991 Apr. 2; 1493 (Item 28)
  - Contact sheet 1494, 1991 Apr. 5; 1494 (Item 28)
    "Los Angeles, CA; Gary Snyder at Pitzer College"
    Pitzer College
  - Contact sheet 1495, 1991 Apr. 5; 1495 (Item 28)
  - Contact sheet 1496, 1991 Apr. 6; 1496 (Item 28)
    "Phoenix, AZ; Allen Ginsberg self portrait"
  - Contact sheet 1497, 1991 Apr. 12; 1497 (Item 28)
    New York City; Virginia; Allen Ginsberg self portrait; kitchen window views